{
  "level": 4,
  "unit": 6,
  "vocabulary": [
    {
      "week": "12",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is _____________ is able to be replaced or restored.",
          "answer": "renewable"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Something that is _____________ is hard or impossible to believe.",
          "answer": "incredible"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When something is _____________ , it is changed in its character or condition.",
          "answer": "converted"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When you _____________ something, you use it up or destroy it.",
          "answer": "consume"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ are the results of an action or condition.",
          "answer": "consequences"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ is an unplanned or unexpected situation in which something happens at the same time or in the same way.",
          "answer": "coincidence"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When something is _____________ , it works quickly and completely.",
          "answer": "efficient"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When something is _____________ , it is put in place and ready for use or service.",
          "answer": "installed"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "34",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means to have withdrawn or moved back.",
          "answer": "retreated"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "When something is _____________ , it can make someone angry or impatient.",
          "answer": "irritating"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means to lose or have to give up because of some fault, accident, or mistake.",
          "answer": "forfeit"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the power to put up with hardships or difficulties.",
          "answer": "endurance"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ are people from whom one is descended.",
          "answer": "ancestors"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means looked down on as worthless, or scorned.",
          "answer": "despised"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ means to show or feel great respect for a person or thing.",
          "answer": "honor"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ means having or showing strong feeling, purpose, or effort.",
          "answer": "intensity"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ poems have irregular lines and lack a metrical pattern and rhyme scheme.",
          "answer": "free verse"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is the use of sensory words to create a picture in the reader’s mind.",
          "answer": "imagery"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A _____________ , such as “the lake is a mirror,” compares two unlike things without using like or as.",
          "answer": "metaphor"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A person’s _____________ include his or her ancestors.",
          "answer": "roots"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is a cloud of tiny drops of water or other liquid in the air.",
          "answer": "mist"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is a quality that makes one person or thing different from others.",
          "answer": "individuality"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "To _____________ means to eat quickly, in large chunks.",
          "answer": "gobble"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "_____________ is giving human characteristics to anything that is not human.",
          "answer": "personification"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
